You just want to roll it.
Now you can see the lemon's kind of soft.
Give it a good squeeze.
You just want to cut it in half.
Now we've got 2 halves.
Once again, you can go ahead and just wrap one of these up and save it for later, or go ahead and squeeze them both now.
We've got a juicer.
You just want to press down.
As we press down, turn either counterclockwise or clockwise.
It's up to you.
We've got a strainer to catch all of the seeds and some of the pulp, so that's good.
You just want to squeeze.
Then what you want to do is you want to squeeze the edges of the lemon, because as you're squeezing the lemon itself, a lot of the pulp comes out to the edges.
You want to make sure you squeeze all of it.
Keep turning.
Discard this, give it a nice twist, and there you go.
Fresh lemon juice.